http://www.visualapp.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomeDigital MarketingWebsite DesignOur WorkManufacturingLocal & Small BusinessDistribution & SalesOil & GasBusiness ServicesBuilding & ConstructionIndustrial ServicesTransportationNon-Profits & AssociationsOur StoryContact
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Visual App collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.visusalapp.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Visual App.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address and phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We may also collect demographic and interests-reporting data via Google Analytics, among other general non-personal information as provided by Google Analytics.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationVisual App may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.This Privacy Policy was last updated May 5th, 2020. Any changes or modifications to our Privacy Policy may be made at any time, and will then reflect the new date of any such update.See What Your Website Can Do For You972.235.5353First Name*Last Name*Email* Comments / Questions*
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
Go to Top
